and today is the forty-seven
to caraca
people accepted my talk bro
i don't believe it old
man this is going to help me a lot
because I'm having several embezzlements with chevas
I'm doing the shopping
the truffles
all late
moment that doesn't look good
I need to have a better condition you know
to sleep better
You have a good head for thinking
but can't I get there
with my Balenciaga shorts
look here
look at this
and then I went to put on my pants bro
look at the pants
I think it's important for us to maintain tolerance
legal born
O who is saying this to you
but due to circumstances
have good money on the table
fits a little investment
I know that the value of what we do is in the message
but people notice the messenger a lot
has no way
I had to go to a store here to deliver the troupes
people are already there at the post with chevas mano
our tomara that gives a good old man
the guys
bro gives a mistreatment plan here on the Chevrolet parts
there's something missing
even more so the air filter cover
where the air filter fell
chevas doesn't catch at all
part purchase
exchange such as with great detail
is on
you'll probably have to pull him on the rope
but there with the traffic
there's also a bid for a fine there,
right bro
I thought it was rope
goes by winch
thank you brother
take an Anchieta there at the gas station
and it's my family
where the crowd is there
and there I solve bro
start fixing
mission given
it's mission accomplished
long done
is on
but finally the cheba arrived vei
he has a lot of problems
but the important thing is that he's at home bro
valeu hand
this post here is a type
a family for me
look what these guys did
the post owner called bro and spoke
old man is here
I'll pay the winch for you
bora there
that my partner
Roger will drop me off there at the mall bro
now i need to get some old cloth because you're making fun of it
there's no bro
brother beauty
when i saw the price i said
bro you are crazy
I won't pay a hundred and fifty
tale in a shorts
then I had a seventy percent discount bro I thought
now that the chevas has returned
want to see if i can
focus a little more on the business plan
but it's good people
ok we are living one problem at a time
we live one solution at a time
that it's easy to be understood when it's good
nor hand
it's good to be funny when it's bad too
that's it people
good night there
until tomorrow